Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Leo Deaner collection 1902-2006 IBT0022
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Contracts and Agreements, 1942-2002; Series 4; 5.75 Linear Feet
  - General and National Master Freight Agreements, 1942-1998; Series 4 Subseries 1; 2.5 Linear Feet
    - National Master Freight Agreement and Central Pennsylvania Over-the-Road Supplement, 1964; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - National Master Freight Agreement and Relay Supplement, 1964; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - "Bargaining and Wages in Local Cartage", 1966; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - National Master Freight Agreement, 1967; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Central Pennsylvania Mechanics and Office Employees Agreement, 1967; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Central Pennsylvania Steel Haul and Special Commonties Supplemental Agreement, 1967; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Dolly Madison Leasing and Financial Corp. Agreement, February 13, 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - IML Freight Inc. Agreement, April, 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Keebler Co. Agreement, September, 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Yellow Cab Agreement, 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - National Master Freight Agreement, 1970; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Local 776, 1970; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Penn-Harris Taxi Service, 1970; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Central Storage and transfer-Warehouse Division Agreement, April 1972-April 1978; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Drivers Inc. Agreement, October, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - National Master Freight Agreement, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Central Pennsylvania Mechanics and Office Employees Agreement, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - The International Teamster Magazine, 1973 May; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - News Clippings, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Stroehman Brothers co. Agreement, November, 1974-November, 1977; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - National Master Freight Agreement, 1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Central Pennsylvania Mechanics and Office Employees Agreement, 1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - News Clippings, 1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - NMFA Notices and Memoranda, 1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - The International Teamster Magazine, 1976 May; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Teamsters for a Decent Contract, 1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Rite Aid Agreement, June 1978-August 1987; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Keystone Railway Equipment Co., September 1978; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - News Clippings, 1978-1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - National Master Freight Agreement, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - United News Transportation (UNTCO) Agreement, February, 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Harrisburg Importing Distributors Association, June 1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Harrisburg Grocery Co. Agreement, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Central Pennsylvania Mechanics and Office Employees Agreement, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Central Pennsylvania Over-the-Road and Local Cartage Supplement, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - The International Teamster Magazine, 1979 March-May; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - National Master Freight Agreement, 1982; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Central Pennsylvania Mechanics and Office Employees Agreement, 1982; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Central Pennsylvania Over-the-Road and Local Cartage Supplement, 1982; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1982; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - News Clippings, 1981-1982; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - NMFA Relief Rider, 1983; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - National Master Freight Agreement, 1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Central Pennsylvania Mechanics and Office Employees Agreement, 1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - The International Teamster Magazine, 1985 February, May; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Central Pennsylvania Over-the-Road and Local Cartage Supplement, 1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Pilot Freight Carriers Agreement, 1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - News Clippings, 1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Local 776 Correspondence, 1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Company Publications, 1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Local 776 Mileage Rates, 1986-1987; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - National Master Freight Agreement, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Central Pennsylvania Mechanics and Office Employees Agreement, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - NMFA Addendums, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - NMFA Proposals, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - IBT News Releases, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - The International Teamster Magazine, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - NMFA Ballot and Ratification, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Local 776 Correspondence, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - News Clippings, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Contract Expiration List, March 17, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Local 776 Mileage Rates, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - National Master Freight Agreement, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Central Pennsylvania Mechanics and Office Employees Agreement, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - NMFA Proposals, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Highspire Borough Council Contracts, July 19, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Central Pennsylvania Over-the-Road and Local Cartage Supplement, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - NMFA Addendums, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - IBT News Releases, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - News Clippings, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Local 776, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - NMFA Ballots and Ratification, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Central Pennsylvania Over-the-Road and Local Cartage Agreement, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Local 776 Mileage Rates, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - The New Teamster Magazine, 1993 January; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - News Clippings, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - News Clippings, 1993-1994; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - News Clippings, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - News Clippings re: Teamsters Strike, 1994-1995; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - IBT Correspondence, 1993-1994; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Teamsters Strike, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - NMFA Research, 1993-1994; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Company Publications, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Central Pennsylvania Over-the-Road and Local Cartage Supplement, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Teamsters Freight Bulletin, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - NMFA Proposals, 1993-1994; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - National Master Freight Agreement, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Local 776, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - NMFA Ballots and Ratification, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - NMFA Teamster Member Survey, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Teamsters National Freight Industry Negotiating Committee, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Teamster Strike, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Teamsters Freight '98: Roadmap to a Better Future, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - NMFA Ballot, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - NMFA Voting Results, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - National Master Freight Agreement, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Central Pennsylvania Supplement, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Hazardous Materials Training, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Teamsters National Freight Industry Negotiating Committee, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Joint Industry Survey, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Teamsters NMFA Survey, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Teamsters Correspondence, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - News Releases, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Local 776, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - News Clippings, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Teamsters Freight '98: Common Cents about the Freight Industry, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Teamsters Freight Bulletin, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - UPS Contracts, 1970-2002; Series 4 Subseries 2; 3.25 Linear Feet
    This subseries contains Teamsters' contracts with the United Parcel Service, Inc. (UPS) dating from 1970-2002, as well as materials related to the negotiation of these agreements spanning the same years. These include contract proposals, ballots and voting results, supplemental agreements, reports, news clippings, newsletters, news releases, correspondence and e-mails, among a variety of other material. Much of the material relates to IBT Local 776. and other Pennsylvania Teamsters, specifically.
    - UPS Contract, 1970; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - UPS Contract, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - UPS Contract, 1976; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - UPS Contract, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1982; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Local 177 Agreement, 1982; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - UPS Contract Extension, 1985; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - UPS Contract Extension Proposals, 1984; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - News Clippings and Contract Bulletins, 1984; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - UPS Contract, 1987; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - UPS Contract Ballot, 1987; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Central Pennsylvania Supplement, 1987; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Local 776 Proposal Meeting, 1987; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - UPS Contract Proposals, 1987; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence and News Releases, 1986-1987; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Local 623 Supplemental Agreement, 1987; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - 401K Plan, 1987; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1987; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - The International Teamster Magazine, 1987; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Tentative Agreement, 1987; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Wage Progressions and Air Rates, 1987; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Monetary Agreement, 1987; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Central Pennsylvania Negotiations, 1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - The International Teamster Magazine, 1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - UPS Contract, 1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - UPS Correspondence, 1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Summary of Contract Changes, 1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Controlled Substance Testing Agreement, 1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Local 776 Contract Proposals, 1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Eastern Conference Supplements, 1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - IBT Economics Department Report, 1992; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Local 776 Correspondence and News Clippings, 1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - News Clippings, 1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - UPS Contract Draft, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Teamsters Contract Proposals, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Contract Update Newsletter, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Teamsters Membership Survey, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - News Clippings, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Canadian Teamsters Contract Ratification, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - UPS News Clippings, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Teamsters Correspondence, 1992-1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - UPS Air Gateway, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Central Pennsylvania Supplemental Agreement, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Local 776 Correspondence and News Clippings, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - UPS Contract Proposals, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - The New Teamster Magazine, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - UPS Contract, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - "It's Our Contract: We'll Fight For It!", 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Teamster UPS Update Newsletter, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - "The Fight at UPS: The Teamsters' Victory and the Future of the 'New Labor Movement'", 1998; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Pensions, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Teamsters Election Protest, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Tentative Agreement, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Local 776 Correspondence and News Clippings, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Central Pennsylvania Teamsters, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - "Half a Job is Not Enough", 1997 June; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Teamster Bargaining Survey, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Pennsylvania Teamster Correspondence, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Transport Topics, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - UPS Final Offer, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Press Releases, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - UPS Newspaper Ads, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Alexis Herman, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Associated Press Articles, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Chicago News Articles, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Editorials, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Los Angeles Times Articles, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Left-Wing Press Articles, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - New York City News Articles, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - New York Times Articles, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - News Magazine Articles, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Philadelphia News Articles, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Reuter Articles, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Wall Street Journal Articles, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Washington Post Articles, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Settlement Message, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Bear Sterns Shipper Survey, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Lake Success Solidarity Rally, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Petition Drive, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Health and Welfare and Pension Funds, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Strike Vote - Chicago, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - UPS Company Overview, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - UPS Contract Caravan, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Rate Increases, 2001-2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - German Trade Unions, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Teamsters Correspondence, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Hiring Subsidies, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - The Teamster Leader Newsletter, 2001-2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - UPS Airline Mechanics, 2001-2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Thrift Plan, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Full-Time/Part-Time Ratio, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Teamsters/UPS Polling, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Teamsters Mailings, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - US Postal Service, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - "Whatever it Takes" Script Draft, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Teamster Magazine, 2000-2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Michael Eskew, 2001-2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - TDU Contract Bulletin, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Convoy Dispatch, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - "Rank and File Organizing at UPS", 1982; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Rick Gilberg, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Chicago News Articles, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Media Update, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - "Rank and File Power at UPS", 2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - UPS PAC, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - UPS Teamster Bargaining Survey, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - UPS Teamster Locals, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - UPS Logistics, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - John Steger, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Ken Hall, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - UPS Talking Points and Teamster Responses, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Southern Supplement, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Negotiation Timetable, 2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Greg Tarpinian Research, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Teamsters News Releases, 2000-2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Teamsters Website Statistics, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Left-Wing Press Articles, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - James P. Hoffa Speeches, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Contract Campaign Kickoff Rally, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - "UPS Date" Newsletter, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - "Teamster UPS News" Newsletter, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Supplemental Negotiations, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Central Region Supplemental Agreement, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Union Proposals [1/2], 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Union Proposals [2/2], 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Company Proposals, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - News Clippings, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - News Clippings, 2002 January - March; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - News Clippings, 2002 April - June; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - News Clippings, 2002 July; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - News Clippings, 2002 August; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Contract Proposal, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Contract Vote Totals, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Teamsters Correspondence, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - TRAK-UPS Hotline, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Teamsters Communications Department, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - "Six Elements in the Teamsters Victory at UPS", 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Contract Settlement, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Ron Carey, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - UPS Two-Person Committee Meeting, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - 10,000 New Jobs Arbitration, 1997-2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Western Pennsylvania Supplement Vote Totals, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - UPS Stock Plan, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Parcel and Small Package Trade Division Workshop, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Project RISE, 1992-2005; 1999-2005; Series 5; 4.5 Linear Feet
  - Code of Conduct, 2000-2001; Series 5 Subseries 1; 1 Linear Feet
    This subseries contains multiple drafts of Project RISES' Code of Conduct, developed as a set of standards for the Teamsters to avoid the "plague of corruption" and the "intrusion of politics into Union discipline." The drafts span 13 months of development and revision, and include official drafts, confidential drafts, and "red-line" drafts (direct comparisons between two documents). Some correspondence also accompanies most drafts.Topics covered in the Code include expenditure of union money, local union elections, and political activity, as well as proposed enforecement mechanisms.
    - Discussion Draft, 2000 March 28; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Proposed First Draft, 2000 April 19; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Official Draft No. 1, 2000 May 5; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Confidential Draft, 2000 June 1; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Confidential Draft, 2000 July 10; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Confidential Draft, 2000 July 25; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Discussion Draft, 2000 August 8; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Official Draft No. 2, 2000 August 24; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 8)